

Passionate Senior Facebook Marketer with 7+ years of experience, growing my own business from 0 to \$1 million in revenue with Facebook Ads, SEO, Content marketing, Email marketing and Affiliate marketing. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for the Facebook ads projects. Well-versed in programming languages including HTML5, JavaScript, CSS.

BORISLAV DRAGANOV

Phone:

+38978466400

E-Mail:

stelibo@yahoo.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/borislavdraganov1971/

Skill Highlights

- Facebook Ads Manager Expert
- Skill Highlights
- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused

Languages

- English professional working proficiency
- Macedonian Native
- Serbian/Croatian Native or bilingual proficiency

Experience

09/2019 - present

Senior Facebook Marketer at Cubatica, Facebook Marketing Partner, Sydney AU

- Cooperate with designers to create ad creatives and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Develop Ad Campaign project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.

Senior Facebook Marketer at Maximum Marketing

(mirkoceselkoski.me)

06/2016 - present

- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex funnels for corporate clients.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- SEO
- Digital marketing strategies
- Web analytics
- Display marketing
- Video advertising
- Copywriting
- Native advertising

Personal Projects

2013-present

 HealthAndLovePage.com, DiabetesHealthPage.com, GottaDoTheRightThing.com - personal blogs.

Education

1990-1995

Bachelor of Economics and Management - Ss. Cyril and Methodius University, Skopje